#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/jeanette-griffin-074545b (LinkedIn)

# Jeanette Griffin

Senior Vice Presidnet at Wells Fargo Bank, NA Greater Philadelphia Area

## Summary

Senior Financial Professional with extensive broad-based experience in portfolio and risk management, credit underwriting and relationship management, focused in the healthcare sector. Offers strong analytical expertise, particularly as it relates to healthcare clients, and outstanding client relationship skills. Unquestioned commitment to providing quality customer service.

### **Key Capabilities:**

\*Strong credit, underwriting and relationship management skills with experience in Healthcare, Defense & Aerospace, large corporate and middle market lending.

\*Demonstrated ability to adapt methods of conducting business to meet the needs of a changing organization and industry. Experience with increasing responsibilities in results-oriented environment.

\*Thorough understanding of system development and the application of technology to the workplace.

\*Partner effectively with internal and external parties to ensure optimal outcomes.

Specialties: Healthcare industry expertise

## Experience

Wells Fargo Bank
Senior Vice President
2009 - Present (11 years)
Risk Officer in Special Assets Management

Wachovia Securities Director 1989 - 2008 (19 years)

First Union National Bank

4 years

Director, Portfolio Manager, Healthcare Finance Group 2003 - 2005 (2 years)

VP, Portfolio Manager, Healthcare Finance Group 2001 - 2003 (2 years)

First Union National Bank Vice President, Underwriter 1996 - 2000 (4 years)

First Fidelity Bank Relationship Banker, AVP 1993 - 1996 (3 years)

First Fidelity Bank Leasing Group Financial Analyst 1989 - 1993 (4 years)

Coopers & Lybrand Senior Audit Staff 1987 - 1989 (2 years)

## Education

Temple University MBA · (1993 - 1996)

University of Delaware BS, Accounting · (1982 - 1986)